James Luther Adams Papers
James Luther Adams Papers
- Correspondence
  - Fenn, Roger C. (Box 37)
  - Fenn, Memorial Fund (Box 37)
  - Fennwick, William, Dolly and Chalman (Box 37)
  - Ferenez, Joseph (Box 37)
  - Ferm, Vergilius (Box 37)
  - Ferm, Deane William (Box 37)
  - Ferraro, Joseph W. (Box 37)
  - Fewkes, Richard (Box 37)
  - FIALA (Box 37)
  - Fichter, Rev. J.H. (Box 37)
  - Fiedler, L. W. (Box 37)
  - Fidley, Harold (Box 37)
  - Finch, Henry (Box 37)
  - Finekh, A. (Box 37)
  - First Church Chicago (Box 37)
  - First Unitarian Church, Chicago (Box 37)
  - Fisher, Dorothy C. (Box 37)
  - Fischer, Gerhard (Box 37)
  - Fischoff, Ephraim, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Fitchen, A.N. (Box 38)
  - Fitzpatrick, Gerald (Box 38)
  - Fitzpatrick, Mallory (Box 38)
  - Flanders, Leon (Box 38)
  - Fleck, P. (Box 38)
  - Fletcher, Prof. Joseph F., 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Fletcher, Ronald (Box 38)
  - Fletcher, Verne and Alice (Box 38)
  - Flint, J.T. (Box 38)
  - Flint, Robert W. (Box 38)
  - Foote, Henry Wilder (Box 38)
  - Forbes, Elliot (Box 38)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 38)
  - Forman, Charles (Box 38)
  - Fortress Press (Box 38)
  - Fortune (Box 39)
  - Forwalter, John (Box 39)
  - Foundation, Arts, Religion, Culture, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Fowler, Newton B., Jr. (Box 39)
  - Fowler, James (Box 39)
  - Fox, Charles (Box 39)
  - Fox, George (Box 39)
  - Fox, Marvin (Box 39)
  - Fraenkel, Ernst, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Fraggos, Charles (Box 39)
  - Frank, Lawrence K. (Box 39)
  - Fraser, Donald M. (Box 39)
  - Frederickson, Ralph (Box 39)
  - Free Press, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Freeburg, John (Box 40)
  - Freeman, Anne (Box 40)
  - Freedon School (Box 40)
  - Freeman, Roger MacClement (Box 40)
  - Frei, Hans (Box 40)
  - French, D. (Box 40)
  - French, R. (Box 40)
  - Friedmann, R. (Box 40)
  - Friedrich, Carl J. (Box 40)
  - Fritchman, Stephan H. (Box 40)
  - Fukuyama, Y., 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Fulbright (Box 40)
  - Fuller, Mrs. Barbara (Box 40)
  - Fuller, Don (Box 40)
  - Fuller, John C. (Box 40)
  - Fund for the Republic (Box 40)
  - Funk, Peter V.K. (Box 40)
  - Fa-Fu, 7 folders (Box 41)
  - Gaebler, Max (Box 41)
  - Gaebler, P. (Box 41)
  - Gale, Bradford (Box 41)
  - Galli, Fr. Guido (Box 41)
  - Gandy, Samuel L. (Box 41)
  - Gardiner, Robert (Box 41)
  - Gardiner, Prof. E.C. (Box 41)
  - Gardner, George H. (Box 41)
  - Garrard, L.A. (Box 41)
  - Garver, R. (Box 41)
  - Gaus, J.M. (Box 41)
  - Gehrmann, D. (Box 41)
  - Geldbach, Erich (Box 41)
  - Gelsey, Rudolf (Box 41)
  - General Theological Library, Boston (Box 41)
  - German Consulate (Box 41)
  - Gerig, V.M. (Box 41)
  - German Engagements (Box 41)
  - Germantown (Box 41)
  - Germantown Unitarian Church (Box 41)
  - Gessert, R. (Box 42)
  - Gewirtz, Rabbi Leonard B. (Box 42)
  - Geyer, Alan (Box 42)
  - Gibb, H.A.R. (Box 42)
  - Gibbons, Ray (Box 42)
  - Gibbs, Lee (Box 42)
  - Gilbert, Richard (Box 42)
  - Gilden, Bert (Box 42)
  - Gill, John (Box 42)
  - Gillingham, David (Box 42)
  - Gillugly, Robert R. (Box 42)
  - Gilmartin, Aron (Box 42)
  - Gilmon, J. Herbert,Jr. (Box 42)
  - Gilmore, Myron (Box 42)
  - Gilmour, S.M. (Box 42)
  - Gilpatrick, Jean & Tom (Box 42)
  - Gittelsohn, Roland (Box 42)
  - Glee Club (Box 42)
  - Glock, Charles (Box 42)
  - Godbey, J.C. (Box 42)
  - Goen, C.C. (Box 42)
  - Göhler, J. (Box 42)
  - Goethals, M. (Box 42)
  - Goethe Society of New England Inc. (Box 42)
  - Gold, Ben-Zion (Box 42)
  - Goldberg, A.J. (Box 42)
  - Golding, Martin P. (Box 43)
  - Goldstein, Dr. M.M. (Box 43)
  - Goldall, O.D. (Box 43)
  - Goodenough, Dr. Evelyn W. (Box 43)
  - Goodenough, Erwin (Box 43)
  - Gordh, Prof. George (Box 43)
  - Gottwald, N.K. (Box 43)
  - Gould Farm (Box 43)
  - Graham, Arthur (Box 43)
  - Grant, Martin (Box 43)
  - Grant, Robert M. (Box 43)
  - Gray, Smith (Box 43)
  - Great Books Foundation (Box 43)
  - Greeley, Dana M., 3 folders (Box 43)
  - Green, Douglas (Box 43)
  - Green, William B. (Box 43)
  - Greene, Frank C. (Box 43)
  - Greene, Richardson (Box 43)
  - Greenleaf, Robert K., 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Gregory, W. Edgar (Box 43)
  - Grieve, George (Box 43)
  - Griffin, Frederick R. (Box 43)
  - Griffin Fund (Box 44)
  - Griswold, E.N. (Box 44)
  - Grose, George Benedict (Box 44)
  - Grossman, M. (Box 44)
  - Grossman, W. (Box 44)
  - Grove Press (Tropic of Cancer) (Box 44)
  - Grundemeier, Ernst (Box 44)
  - Gschaedler, Andre (Dr.), 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Gudmundson, V.E. (Box 44)
  - Gustafson, James M. (Box 44)
  - Guy, Rev. William V. (Box 44)
  - Ga-Gu, 7 folders (Box 44)
  - H, K. (Box 44)
  - Haac, Oscar A. (Box 44)
  - Hackbarth, Sally (Box 44)
  - Hacker, Louis M. & Beatrice (Box 44)
  - Hager, Warren A. (Box 44)
  - Haiz, Donna (Box 44)
  - Hall, Cameron P. (Box 44)
  - Hall, Charles A.M. (Box 44)
  - Hall, Gordon D., 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Hall, Jerome (Box 45)
  - Hall, Winfield S. (Box 45)
  - Halvorson, L., 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Hammon, Jack K. (Box 45)
  - Hammon, M. (Box 45)
  - Hanburg, Dom Michael (Box 45)
  - Hanchett, Paul (Box 45)
  - Handy, Robert T. (Box 45)
  - Hanley, Robert W. (Box 45)
  - Hanner, James C. (Box 45)
  - Hanson, Miles, Jr. (Box 45)
  - Hanslow, K. (Box 45)
  - Happe, Allen (Box 45)
  - Harn, Ichiro (Box 45)
  - Harap, Louis (Box 45)
  - Harcourt Brace (Box 45)
  - Hardwick, Charley D. (Box 45)
  - Hardy, Sir A. (Box 45)
  - Hargadon, Thomas (Box 45)
  - Haroutunian, Joseph (Box 45)
  - Harper & Row, 4 folders (Box 45, 46)
  - Harrington, D. (Box 46)
  - Harris, Abram L. (Box 46)
  - Harris, M. LaFayette (Pres.) (Box 46)
  - Harshbarger, Dr. Luther (Box 46)
  - Hartford Theological Seminary (Box 46)
  - Hartshorne, Charles (Box 46)
  - Hartshorne, M. Holmes (Box 46)
  - Harvard (general) (Box 46)
  - Harvard (libraries) (Box 46)
  - Harvard (faculty retirement) (Box 46)
  - Harvard (higher degrees), 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Harvard Divinity, 8 folders (Box 47, 48)
  - Harvard Glee Club (Box 48)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 48)
  - Harvard Law School Forum (Box 48)
  - Harvard University Memorial Church (Box 48)
  - Harvard University Visiting Scholars Pro-gram (Box 48)
  - Harvard University Press (Box 48)
  - Haskell, Ellery B. (Box 49)
  - Hassinger, Howard H. (Box 49)
  - Haulerwas, Stanley (Box 49)
  - Hauge, Reidar (Box 49)
  - Havens, Joseph & Teresina (Box 49)
  - Hawley, William (Box 49)
  - Haworth, Robert (Box 49)
  - Hayes, Christopher (Box 49)
  - Hayes, Donna (Box 49)
  - Hayes, R.E. (Box 49)
  - Hayward, J. Frank & Catherine (Box 49)
  - Hayward, J.Y. (Box 49)
  - Hazard, Priscilla (Box 49)
  - Health (Box 49)
  - Heddendorf, Russell (Box 49)
  - Heering, H.J. (Box 49)
  - Heim, Lotte (Box 49)
  - Heimann, Edward, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Heisler, Francis (Box 50)
  - Helm, Thomas (Box 50)
  - Helverson, R.N., 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Henderson, G. (Box 50)
  - Hendrickson, Glenn I. (Box 50)
  - Henel, Ingeborg (Box 50)
  - Henry, Carl F. H. (Box 50)
  - Hensley, Francis W. (Box 50)
  - Henzlick, William (Box 50)
  - Herbst, J. (Box 50)
  - Herrick, Adele R. (Box 50)
  - Hersey, Benjamin (Box 50)
  - Herstein, Lillian (Box 50)
  - Heselton, John (Box 50)
  - Heyl, Elizabeth (Box 50)
  - Heyne, William P. (Box 50)
  - Hicks, Edward (Box 50)
  - Hidding, K.A.H. (Box 50)
  - Highlander (Box 50)
  - Highlander Center (Box 51)
  - Hill, Clifford (Box 51)
  - Hilliard, Curtis & Helen (Box 51)
  - Hiltner, Seward, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Hillerbrand, H.J. (Box 51)
  - Hilton, R. (Box 51)
  - Hinderlie, C.L. (Box 51)
  - Hindle, Irene (Box 51)
  - Hindreth, Marie (Mrs. Harry F.) (Box 51)
  - Hirai, Naofusa (Box 51)
  - Hirning, L. Clovis (Box 51)
  - Hirsch, Ruth (Box 51)
  - Hisamatsu, Shinichi (Box 51)
  - Hoagland, Robert S. (Box 51)
  - Hodgin, Ellis (Box 51)
  - Hodnett, James (Box 51)
  - Hoehler, H. (Box 51)
  - Hoenderdaal, G. (Box 51)
  - Hoffman, Clifton G. (Box 51)
  - Hoffsommer, H. (Box 51)
  - Hofmann, Hans (Box 51)
  - Hoge, Dean (Box 51)
  - Holden, Robert (Box 51)
  - Holden, William L (Box 52)
  - Holmer, Earl A. (Box 52)
  - Holmes, Dunbar (Box 52)
  - Holmes, Frank O., 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Holmes, J.H. (Box 52)
  - Holmes, Lincoln (Box 52)
  - Holmes, Robert H. (Box 52)
  - Holmer, Earl A. (Box 52)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston (Box 52)
  - Homans, Peter (Box 52)
  - Honigsheim, Paul (Box 52)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 52)
  - Hopper, C. Leon (Box 52)
  - Hooper, J. Harry (Box 52)
  - Hopkins, Jeannette E. (Box 52)
  - Horton, Dean Douglas, 3 folders (Box 52, 53)
  - Horton, Myles (Box 53)
  - Horton, Walter Marshall (Box 53)
  - Horvath, Wayne W., 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Houff, William H. (Box 53)
  - Hough, Joseph C., Jr. (Box 53)
  - Hough, Amorf von (Box 53)
  - Hound & Horn Inc. (Box 53)
  - Howard, George G. (Box 53)
  - Howard, Stephen D. (Box 53)
  - Howard University (Box 53)
  - Howe, Revel, L. (Box 53)
  - Howland, Howard & Bette (Box 53)
  - Howlett, Duncan (Box 53)
  - Hromadka, J.L. (Box 53)
  - Hrumatko, W. (Box 53)
  - Hruby, B. (Box 53)
  - Huckabee, Weyman C. (Box 53)
  - Hudson, Terry (Box 53)
  - Hudson, William (Box 53)
  - Huf, S. (Box 53)
  - Huff, Richard H. (Box 53)
  - Hughes, Stuart (Box 53)
  - Hull, Denison B. (Box 53)
  - Hume, Robert R. (Box 53)
  - Humphrey-Muskie (Box 53)
  - Hundley, Robert M. (Box 53)
  - Hunt, Bryan (Box 53)
  - Hunter, Evelyn (Mrs. Guy F.) (Box 53)
  - Hunter, Howard (Box 53)
  - Hunter, Willard (Box 53)
  - Hutch, R. (Box 54)
  - Hutchins, Francis S. (Box 54)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (Box 54)
  - Hutchison, W.R. & William T. (Box 54)
  - Ha-Hy, 7 folders (Box 54)
  - Iberia Airlines of Spain (Box 55)
  - Ibraham, Sargon Y. (Box 55)
  - Ice, Jackson Lee (Box 55)
  - Iggers, George, 4 folders (Box 55)
  - Iino, David N. (Box 55)
  - Iliff School (Box 55)
  - Imaoka, Shinichiro (Box 55)
  - Imeh, Nnah A. H. (Box 55)
  - Impey, Richard (Box 55)
  - Independent Citizens Committee of the Arts and Sciences (Box 55)
  - Independent Voters Committee of Illinois (Box 56)
  - Infield, Dr. H. (Box 56)
  - Inouye, Shin-Ichi (Box 56)
  - Institute of Pastoral Care (Box 56)
  - Institute for Social Research (Box 56)
  - Institute on Man and Science (Box 56)
  - Interdoc - International Documentation and Information Center (Box 56)
  - Interseminary (Box 56)
  - I.A.H.R. - International Association - History of Religions, 3 folders (Box 56)
  - International Christian University (Box 56)
  - IFCO - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization (Box 56)
  - The Intimate Strangers and the Younger Intimate Strangers (Box 56)
  - Investment Committee (Box 56)
  - Iowa, University of (Box 56)
  - Issac, Ephraim (Box 57)
  - Ishii, T. (Box 57)
  - Ishizu, Prof. T. (Box 57)
  - Israel, Consul (Box 57)
  - Israel Express, Inc (Box 57)
  - Israeli Information Services (Box 57)
  - Iwai, Timothy, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - I (Box 57)
  - Jack, Dr. Homer (Box 57)
  - Jackson, George (Box 57)
  - Jackson, Gordon (Box 57)
  - Jackson, Jesse (Box 57)
  - Jackson, Robert S. (Box 57)
  - Jacobs, Paul (Box 57)
  - Jacobsen, William R. (Box 57)
  - Jacobsen, N.P., 3 folders (Box 57, 58)
  - Jacoby, Russell, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Jamison, A.L. (Box 58)
  - Janes, Kelly (Box 58)
  - Jansen, Elly (Box 58)
  - Jencks, Christopher (Box 58)
  - Jehring, J.J. (Box 58)
  - Jenkins, Canon David E. (Box 58)
  - Jenney, Ray (Box 58)
  - Jentsch, Rudolf (Box 58)
  - John Knox Press (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Avery R. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Birger J.C. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, C. Dale (Box 58)
  - Johnson, David A. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Edward A. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Howard L. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Nicholas (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Paul (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Raymond B. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Robert A. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, Roger W. (Box 58)
  - Johnson, T. Walter (Box 58)
  - Johnson, William D. (Box 58)
  - Misc. Johnsons (Box 58)
  - Johnston, Gilbert Lee (Box 58)
  - Johnston, J.D. (Box 59)
  - Joliot-Curie, Frederic (Box 59)
  - Jones, Don (Box 59)
  - Jones, Ella M. (Box 59)
  - Jones, Harry I. (Box 59)
  - Jones, John Paul (Box 59)
  - Jones, Keith E. (Box 59)
  - Jones, Llewellyn (Box 59)
  - Jones, Robert (Box 59)
  - Jones, William R. (Box 59)
  - Jones (other) (Box 59)
  - Jonsen, Albert R. (Box 59)
  - Jordahl, Neil (Box 59)
  - Joughin, Louis (Box 59)
  - Journal of the American Academy of Religion (Box 59)
  - Journal of Bible and Religion (Box 59)
  - Journal of Church and State (Box 59)
  - Journal of Current Social Issues (Box 59)
  - Journal of Liberal Religion (Box 59)
  - Journal of Religion (Box 59)
  - Journal of Voluntary Action Research (JVAR) (Box 59)
  - Joy, Charles R. (Box 59)
  - Judicial Review Bill (Box 59)
  - Junker, Theodore (Box 59)
  - J (Box 59)
  - Kafka, Hvezdon (Box 60)
  - Kallen, H.M. (Box 60)
  - Kalter, R. (Box 60)
  - Kao, Charles (Box 60)
  - Kaplan, Jeremiah (Box 60)
  - Kapp, Max (Box 60)
  - Kappelle, D.W. (Box 60)
  - Kato, Soichi (Box 60)
  - Katz, W. (Box 60)
  - Kaucher, Albert N. (Box 60)
  - Kaufman, Gordon D. (Box 60)
  - Kaufman, Fritz and Luise (Box 60)
  - Kaufman, Peter (Box 60)
  - Kawase, Ken'ichiro (Box 60)
  - Keddy, Jane E. (Box 60)
  - Keene, J. Calvin (Box 60)
  - Keeney, William (Box 60)
  - Keeton, Morris (Box 60)
  - Kegley, Charles W. (Box 60)
  - Kellaway, Richard A. (Box 60)
  - Kelly, R.J.,S.J. (Box 60)
  - Kenny, Herbert A. (Box 60)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 60)
  - Kennedy, Robert (Box 60)
  - Kent, Robert (Box 60)
  - Keohane, R. (Box 60)
  - Key to the Route of Social Science (Box 60)
  - Kidwai, A.H. (Box 60)
  - Kielty, J. (Box 61)
  - Kilgallen, John J. (Box 61)
  - Kim, J.K. (Box 61)
  - Kimball, Richard G., 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Kincheloe, S.C. (Box 61)
  - King, Donald B. (Box 61)
  - King, Drue (Box 61)
  - King, Martin Luther (Box 61)
  - King, W.L. (Box 61)
  - Kirshner (Box 61)
  - Kishimoto (Box 61)
  - Kitagawa, Joseph (Box 61)
  - Klapwijk, J. (Box 61)
  - Klemme, Huber F. (Box 61)
  - Klimkeit, Hans (Box 61)
  - Kline, Mary (Box 61)
  - Kloetzli, Walter (Box 61)
  - Knight, Frank (Box 62)
  - Knight, W.R. (Box 62)
  - Knoxville (Box 62)
  - Koch, Leo (Box 62)
  - Koenig, Robert E. (Box 62)
  - Koester, Helmut (Box 62)
  - Koffler, Anna (Box 62)
  - Komonia (Box 62)
  - Kojrma, Gunzo (Box 62)
  - Kolden, Marc (Box 62)
  - Konko-Kyo (Box 62)
  - Kontos, G.W. (Box 62)
  - Koonan, Ruth (Box 62)
  - Korwin-Rhodes (Box 62)
  - Kosa, Dr. John (Box 62)
  - Koracs, Lajos (Box 62)
  - Kovar, Dr. Frantisek (Box 62)
  - Kraemer, William S. (Box 62)
  - Kraft, Julius (Box 62)
  - Krapf, Gustav-Adolf (Box 62)
  - Krejei, Jaroslav (Box 62)
  - Krichels, Deborah (Box 62)
  - Kriebel, S. (Box 62)
  - Kring, Walter D.(2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Krueger, Delton (Box 62)
  - Kubik, Miss Eva (Box 62)
  - Kucheman, Clark I (Box 62)
  - Kuebler, Ernest (Box 62)
  - Kuntz, Paul G. (Box 62)
  - Kupsch, Edward (Box 63)
  - Kurman, M. (Box 63)
  - Kwak, Hoon (Box 63)
  - Ka-Ky, 9 folders (Box 63)
  - LaPiana, G. (Box 63)
  - Ladd, John (Box 63)
  - Lakoff, S. (Box 63)
  - Lam, Elizabeth (Box 63)
  - Lamm, H. (Box 63)
  - Lamont, Corliss (Box 63)
  - Lancaster, Beverly (Box 63)
  - Landis, Benson J. (Box 63)
  - Lane, Dorothy (Box 63)
  - Lane, Edwin (Box 63)
  - Lane, Harold E. (Box 63)
  - Lange, Bertha (Box 63)
  - Langer, W.L. (Box 63)
  - Langinrichs, R.A. (Box 63)
  - Larson, Martin A. (Box 63)
  - Lashlee, Ernest (Box 63)
  - Lathrop, John Howland (Box 63)
  - Lauriat, N.P. (Box 63)
  - Lavan, S. (Box 64)
  - Lawler, Helen M. (Box 64)
  - Lawrence, Frank K. (Box 64)
  - Laws, John (Box 64)
  - Lawson, Robert W. (Box 64)
  - Lawthers, R. (Box 64)
  - Laymen's League (Box 64)
  - Laymen's Movement for a Christian World, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Lazzaro, R. (Box 64)
  - Leach, Henry Goddard (Box 64)
  - Leaman, John (Box 64)
  - Leaming, Hugo and Marjorie (Box 64)
  - Learned, Edmund (Box 64)
  - Lease, Gary (Box 64)
  - Lee, A.M. (Box 64)
  - Lee, Carleton L. (Box 64)
  - Lee, Conrad (Box 64)
  - Lee, Dorothy (Box 64)
  - Lee, E.G. (Box 64)
  - Lee, K.R. (Box 64)
  - Lee, Louise (Box 64)
  - Lee, Paul A. (Box 65)
  - Lee, Robert (Box 65)
  - Leemans, A.F. (Box 65)
  - LeFevre, P. (Box 65)
  - LeGates, John (Box 65)
  - Lehman, Edward C. Jr. (Box 65)
  - Lehman, Robert S. (Box 65)
  - Lehmann, Paul (Box 65)
  - Lehner, Felix (Box 65)
  - Leibrecht, Walter (Box 65)
  - Leiffer, Murray A. (Box 65)
  - LeFerne, Platzhobb (Box 65)
  - Lemert, C.C. (Box 65)
  - Lenkersdorf, Karl, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Lens, Sid (Box 65)
  - Lenz, Kurt (Box 66)
  - Leonard, Roydon (Box 66)
  - Lepawsky, Albert (Box 66)
  - LePlay, House & Press (Box 66)
  - Lerner, Deana (Box 66)
  - Lerner, Deana & Robert (Box 66)
  - Lerner, Leo A. (Box 66)
  - Leslie, Kenneth (Box 66)
  - Levenson, Rusty (Box 66)
  - Levenson, Alan (Box 66)
  - Lewis, Andrian (Box 66)
  - Lewis, Fred R. (Box 66)
  - Lewis, Lester (Box 66)
  - Liberal Context (Box 66)
  - Liberal Religious Youth (Box 66)
  - Library (Box 67)
  - Library Comm. (Box 67)
  - Library, Hds. (Box 67)
  - Library of Living Theology (Box 67)
  - Lindsley, Karen (Box 67)
  - Lions, Zelda (Box 67)
  - Lipman, E. (Box 67)
  - Lissen, Ute (Box 67)
  - Littell, Franklin H., 4 folders (Box 67)
  - Little, David, 2 folders (Box 67, 68)
  - Little, H. Ganse, 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Littlefair, D. (Box 68)
  - Livezey, Lowell (Box 68)
  - Lochman, J.M. (Box 68)
  - Loder, James E., Jr. (Box 68)
  - Loewenfeld, Gunther (Box 68)
  - Loeser, Herta (Box 68)
  - Lohman, Joseph D. (Box 68)
  - Long, Alva C. (Box 68)
  - Long, Edward (Box 68)
  - Long, Herbert (Box 68)
  - Longkjaer, Erik A. (Box 68)
  - Looff, Hans (Box 68)
  - Loomer, Bernard M. (Box 68)
  - Loomis, D. (Box 68)
  - Loos, William (Box 68)
  - Lorch, Iris (Box 68)
  - Lorinez, M. (Box 68)
  - Lotchin, L. (Box 69)
  - Lothrop, Donald J. (Box 69)
  - Lotz, Denton (Box 69)
  - Loubser, Jan (Box 69)
  - Love, Thomas T. (Box 69)
  - Lovekin, Allen B. (Box 69)
  - Lovell, William (Box 69)
  - Lovely, Bill (Box 69)
  - Lovely, N.W. (Box 69)
  - Lowe, Victor (Box 69)
  - Luce, Robert W. (Box 69)
  - Luening, Eugene (Box 69)
  - Lund, R.W. (Box 69)
  - Lyman, Mrs. H. (Box 69)
  - Lynn, Robert (Box 69)
  - Lyons, Charlotte (Box 69)
  - Lyons, Philip (Box 69)
  - Lyttle, Charles H. (Box 69)
  - La-Le, 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Li-Ly, 4 folders (Box 70)
  - McAfee, Malcolm (Box 70)
  - McCagg, Miss Katherine (Box 70)
  - McCann, Richard (Box 70)
  - McCarren Act (Box 70)
  - McCloskey, M. (Box 70)
  - McCormack, John W. (Box 70)
  - McCulloch, Dr. Frank W. (Box 70)
  - McCulloch, Mary (Box 70)
  - McDargh, John (Box 70)
  - McDowell, Arthur G. (Box 70)
  - McGiffert, A.C.(2 folders) (Box 70)
  - MacGilvrn, Ralph A. (Box 70)
  - McGinty, Lawrence E. (Box 70)
  - McGrath, Doyle and Phair (Box 70)
  - McGraw Hill (Box 70)
  - McJenkin, William D. (Box 70)
  - McKey, Miles R. (Box 70)
  - McKinney, Donald W. (Box 70)
  - MacLean, Angus (Box 70)
  - Maclean, Ken (Box 70)
  - McLean, M. (Box 70)
  - McLean, S.D. (Box 70)
  - Macmillian Co. (Box 70)
  - MacNair, Luther (Box 70)
  - MacNeill, John (Box 70)
  - MacPherson, Robert H. (Box 70)
  - Macquarrie, J. (Box 70)
  - Magazines (Box 70)
  - Magistro, Charles F., 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Maguire, Daniel C. (Box 70)
  - Maguire, Michael John (Box 70)
  - Maher, J. (Box 71)
  - Mahoney, Thomas H.D. (Box 71)
  - Maier, Eugene I. (Box 71)
  - Maier, Eugene II (Box 71)
  - Malcolm, Norman (Box 71)
  - Mallinckrodt, Edward (Box 71)
  - Marco, Joyce (Box 71)
  - Marcus, R. (Box 71)
  - Marichal, Prof. Joan (Box 71)
  - Mark, Edward L. (Box 71)
  - Marsh, John (Box 71)
  - Marshall, George N. (Box 71)
  - Marshall, Ken (Box 71)
  - Marshfield, George W. (Box 71)
  - Marti, Fritz (Box 71)
  - Martin, James A., Jr. (Box 71)
  - Martin, Norman H. (Box 71)
  - Martin, William C. (Box 71)
  - Marty, Martin E. (Box 71)
  - Mass Coalition (Box 71)
  - M.I.T. (Box 71)
  - Massachusets Council of Churches (Box 71)
  - Masurager, R. (Box 72)
  - Mathews, Robert E. (Box 72)
  - Mateer, William C. (Box 72)
  - Mathewson, Robert C. (Box 72)
  - Matson, Howard, 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Matthes, J. (Box 72)
  - May, Rollo (Box 72)
  - May, William (Box 72)
  - Mayers, Ronald B. (Box 72)
  - Meade, Betsy (Box 72)
  - Meadville Theological School, 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Meardon, Arnold J. (Box 72)
  - Mecartney, John M. (Box 72)
  - Mecham, William J. (Box 72)
  - Mehrotra, Raj N. (Box 72)
  - Meisel, Donald (Box 72)
  - Meland, Prof. Benard (Box 72)
  - Memorial University of Newfoundland (Box 72)
  - Mende, Georg (Box 72)
  - Mendelsohn, J. (Box 72)
  - Mendelsohn, Edward J. (Box 72)
  - Merritt, Justine (Box 72)
  - Meserve, H.C. (Box 73)
  - Metcalf, J.R. (Box 73)
  - Metropolitan (Box 73)
  - Metz, John B. (Box 73)
  - Metzger, Beri (Box 73)
  - Meyer, Eugene (Box 73)
  - Meyer, Gerhard (Box 73)
  - Meyerson, M. (Box 73)
  - Michaelson, Robert S. (Box 73)
  - Michalis, Clarence F. (Box 73)
  - Michigan (Box 73)
  - Midgley, Louis D. (Box 73)
  - Millard, A. Douglas (Box 73)
  - Millard, Douglas (Box 73)
  - Millard, R.M. (Box 73)
  - Miller, Bob S. (Box 73)
  - Miller, Rev. D.E. (Box 73)
  - Miller, Helen Rand (Box 73)
  - Miller, O.W. (Box 74)
  - Miller, Dayson (Box 74)
  - Miller, Sam H. (Box 74)
  - Miller, William Robert (Box 74)
  - Mills, Edgar (Box 74)
  - Mincar, Lawrence (Box 74)
  - Ministers Club, 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Minor, William S. (Box 74)
  - Mire, J. (Box 74)
  - Misner, P. (Box 74)
  - Mitchell, Howard (Box 74)
  - Mitchell, J. (Box 74)
  - Mochizuki, Ken-ichiroh (Box 74)
  - Modschiedler, John C. (Box 74)
  - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 74)
  - Moellering, Ralph L. (Box 74)
  - Moehling, Karl A. (Box 75)
  - Moehlman, Arthur H. (Box 75)
  - Moffat, Robert C.L. (Box 75)
  - Mondale, R. Lester (Box 75)
  - Mondale, Lester (Box 75)
  - Moodie, T. Dunbar (Box 75)
  - Moore, Charles (Box 75)
  - Moore, Christopher (Box 75)
  - Moore, Hugh (Box 75)
  - Morgan, Bruce (Box 75)
  - Morgan, Kenneth W. (Box 75)
  - Mormonism (Box 75)
  - Morris, William S. (Box 75)
  - Morrison, Charles C. (Box 75)
  - Morrison, Linda Carol (Box 75)
  - Morrison, Truman K. (Box 75)
  - Moseley, J. Edward (Box 75)
  - Moss, J.B. (Box 75)
  - Moulton, Frank (Box 75)
  - Mow, Joseph (Box 75)
  - Mowrer, Ernest R. (Box 75)
  - Muder, Milton E. (Box 75)
  - Muelder, Walter (Box 75)
  - Mueller, Gotthold (Box 75)
  - Muller, Gerhard (Box 75)
  - Mueller, Paul (Box 75)
  - Mumford, Lewis (Box 76)
  - Munsby, Denys L. (Box 76)
  - Munk, Carl (Box 76)
  - Munsell, Alex (Box 76)
  - Munson, Paul N.L., Jr. (Box 76)
  - Murdock, Virgil (Box 76)
  - Murray, Irving R. (Box 76)
  - Murren, J. Keir (Box 76)
  - Music Committee (Box 76)
  - Muste, A.J. (Box 76)
  - Myers, Lucille (Box 76)
  - Myers, R.E. (Box 76)
  - Ma-My, 7 folders (Box 76)
  - Nachlas, M. (Box 76)
  - Naef, Emile (Box 76)
  - Nagatomi, M. (Box 76)
  - Nakamura, Hajime (Box 76)
  - Nakayama, Shozen (Box 77)
  - National Citizens Political Action Committee (Box 77)
  - National Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism (Box 77)
  - National Conference of Christians & Jews (Box 77)
  - National Conference of the Church of Christ (Box 77)
  - National Committee on Tithing in Investment (Box 77)
  - National Institute for the Seriously Ill and Dying (Box 77)
  - National Lutheran Council (Box 77)
  - Naum Keag Steam Cotton Co. Strike, 1933 (Box 77)
  - Nef, John (Box 77)
  - Nelson, Benjamin (Box 77)
  - Nelson, Edward R. (Box 77)
  - Nelson, J. Robert (Box 77)
  - Nelson, James B. (Box 77)
  - Neumann, Kathe (Box 77)
  - Neuendorfer, Ruth (Box 77)
  - Neuenschwander, Ulrich (Box 77)
  - Neusner, Jacob (Box 77)
  - New World (Box 78)
  - Newman, James W. (Box 78)
  - Newman, Hon. Mary B. (Box 78)
  - Newton, Kenneth (Box 78)
  - Nichols, James H. (Box 78)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold (Box 78)
  - Niebuhr, Richard (Box 78)
  - Nielsen, Niels C. (Box 78)
  - Niles, Marion (Box 78)
  - Nisbet, Robert A. (Box 78)
  - Nock, A.D. (Box 78)
  - Noordhoff, Dr. W.R.M. (Box 78)
  - Nordby, George (Box 78)